slideroll.com 2011-04-08

# Privacy Policy - Flash Slideshow Creator, Photo Slideshows for Facebook, MySpace, YouTube, and Everywhere!

### Privacy Policy

This is Slideroll™.com's privacy policy. If you have questions about this policy, or about the information stored in your account, we can be reached via e-mail via our contact form.

#### Types of Information Collected

For each visitor to our site, our web server automatically recognizes the visitor's domain name, referrer, and IP address for statistical purposes. IP addresses of registered clients are displayed in our message board for accountability purposes.

The e-mail addresses of those who register an account with us are used only to verify the client's identity, prevent multiple simultaneous accounts, and send infrequent notices regarding changes in service.

Payment information such as credit card numbers and billing addresses are not stored, nor ever exist on our system. All sensitive client payment data is handled by [Paypal](http://www.paypal.com/) and protected under their [privacy policy.](http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside)

#### How the Information is Used

The information we collect is used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor. **Account information is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.**

Clients can change most account information online. Information that cannot be changed online can be corrected by sending us a message via our contact form.

#### Cookies

The system uses cookies to record session information, so that the client's data files and content remain accessible accross multiple page-views in the site.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on visits to this site and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

#### E-mail Communication

By default, clients must opt in to receive marketing e-mails from us. If you do not want to receive marketing e-mail from us in the future, please change your settings in "My Account". Please note that as long as you have an account with us, there is a small chance we may need to send important system information if there are interruptions or changes in service. By default, registered clients may e-mail eachother via a web-based form. Client's e-mail addresses are never exposed unless they change the default settings in their message board profile. Registered clients may also choose to disallow all client-to-client communication.

#### Security

We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving client data exchanged with our site.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us via our contact form.
